Finding Aid for the Rod Amateau Papers PASC.0088
UCLA Library Special Collections
- GEORGE BURNS AND GRACIE ALLEN SHOW, THE
  - Von Zell's Raises (incl. afterpiece) (Show #217, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/3/56. Draft script dated: 10/10/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Wading Pool at Acapulco, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #246, 1957)
    - Aired: 6/17/57. Draft script dated: 5/15/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Week in New York, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #295, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 6/9/58. Draft script dated: 5/7/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - With or Without Glasses (incl. afterpiece) (Show #269, 1957)
    - Aired: 11/25/57. Draft script dated: 9/25/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Woman in the Car, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #211, 1956)
    - Aired: 10/22/56. Draft script dated: 8/29/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
- GEORGE BURNS SHOW LIVE, THE
  - Show #5, 1958-59 (NBC)
    - Aired: 2/3/59. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Show #1, 1958-59 (NBC)
    - Aired: 12/16/58. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Show #2, 1958-59 (NBC)
    - Aired: 12/30/58. Draft script dated: 12/27/58. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Anna Maria Alberghetti (Show #3, 1958-59) (NBC)
    - Aired: 1/13/59. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, william (Box 14)
  - Rosemary Clooney Guests (Show #4, 1958-59) (NBC)
    - Aired: 1/27/59. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
- GEORGE BURNS SHOW, THE
  - 18 Year Old Novelist, The (Show #5, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 11/18/58. Draft script dated: 9/16/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Breaking Up the Team (Show #15, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 2/3/59. Draft script dated: 12/2/58. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Contract to Sing, The (Show #13, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 1/27/59. Draft script dated: 11/18/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - French Review, The (Show #3, (added scenes in v.9-12, 1958-59), 1957-58)
    - Aired: 10/31/58. Draft script dated: 10/28/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - French Review, The (Show #3, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 10/31/58. Draft script dated: 8/26/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - George and the Private Eye (Show #1, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 10/24/58. Draft script dated: 8/22/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - George Invests in a Record Company (Show #10, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 12/30/58. Draft script dated: 10/28/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - George On Juke Box Jury (Show #16, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 1/3/59. Draft script dated: 12/23/58. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - George Signs Carol Channing (Show #11, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 1/6/59. Draft script dated: 11/4/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - George's Eviction (Show #8, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 12/9/58. Draft script dated: 10/7/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - George's Trial (Show #14, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 1/27/59. Draft script dated: 11/25/58. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Jack Benny Comes Over (Show #2, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 10/31/58. Draft script dated: 9/3/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Jimmie Rodgers Moves in With Ronnie (Show #18, 1958-59)
    - Draft script dated: 1/20/59. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Landlord's Daughter, The (Show #12, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 1/13/58. Draft script dated: 11/11/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Monster Trend, The (Show #7, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 12/2/58. Draft script dated: 9/30/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Monster Trend, The (Show #7, (added scenes in v.9-12, 1958-59), 1957-58)
    - Aired: 12/2/58. Draft script dated: 11/4/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Ronnie Takes An Apartment (Show #17, 1958-59)
    - Draft script dated: 1/6/59. Writer(s): Paul, Norman / Fowler, Keith * Burns, William (Box 14)
  - Tony Martin Visits (Show #6, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 11/25/58. Draft script dated: 9/23/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Walk-On for George, A (Show #4, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 11/11/58. Draft script dated: 9/9/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Wife for Christmas, A (Show #9, 1958-59)
    - Aired: 12/16/58. Draft script dated: 10/14/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 14)
- GILLIGAN'S TRAVELS
  - Say A Few Words Into The Fish (Pilot, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 11/11/63. Writer(s): Schwartz, Sherwood & Elroy * Kallish, Austin (Box 20)
- MANY LOVES OF DOBIE GILLIS, THE
  - Ah, Yer Fadder Wears Army Shoes (Show #35, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/20/61. Writer(s): Gammie, Bill * Shulman, Max (Box 4)
  - All Right, Dobie, Drop the Gun (Show #22, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 10/12/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Almost a Father (Show #27, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 11/2/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 2)
  - Almost a Father (Retakes for Show #27,1959 in vol.37-39, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 11/2/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 4)
  - American Strategy, An (Show #28(added scenes)v.33-36, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 11/3/61. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean * Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - American Strategy, An (Show #28, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 11/3/61. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean * Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - And Now a Word From Our Sponsor (Show #18, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 9/20/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - Around My Room In 80 Days (Show #7, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/3/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence (et al.) * Williams, Maggie (et al.) (Box 3)
  - Baby Shoes (Show #22, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 11/7/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence & Maggie * Shulman, Max (Box 4)
  - Baby Talk (Show #5, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 7/11/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Bachelor Father..and Son (Show #36, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 1/23/62. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Back-to-Nature Boy (Show #35, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 1/16/62. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Battle of Maynard's Beard, The (Show #29, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 12/22/60. Writer(s): Reisner, Dean (Box 4)
  - Be It Ever So Humble (Show #33, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/16/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 4)
  - Beast with Twenty Fingers, The (Show #14, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 8/27/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - Beauty Is Only Kin Deep (Show #34, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 1/11/63. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - Beethoven, Presley and Me (Show #24, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 10/31/62. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 8)
  - Best Dressed Man, The (Show #3, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 4/28/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 1)
  - Big Blunder and Egg Man, The (Show #30, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 11/20/61. Writer(s): Nye, Bud * Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - Big Question, The (Show #17, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 10/11/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max * Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Big Sandwich, The (Show #4, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 5/15/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Gershman, Ben (Box 1)
  - Big Sandwich, The (Show #4, Vol. 5-8, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 6/24/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Gershman, Ben (Box 1)
  - Birth of a Salesman (Show #26, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 10/25/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold * Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - Bitter Feud of Maynard and Dobie, The (Show #18, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 10/18/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel * Amateau, Rod (Box 3)
  - Blue-Tail Fly, The (Show #12, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/26/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 5)
  - Call of the Like Wild, The (Show #35, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 1/25/63. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 8)
  - Caper at the Bijou, The (Show #1, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 1/14/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 1)
  - Chicken Corporal, The (Show #25, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 12/2/60. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 4)
  - Chicken From Outer Space, The (Show #28, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 10/23/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - Competition is the Life of Trade (Show #36, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 1/20/60. Writer(s): Conway, Dick (et al.) * MacLane, Roland (et al.) (Box 2)
  - Competition is the Life of Trade (Show #36, 2nd copy, 1959-60)
    - Draft script dated: 1/20/60. Writer(s): Conway, Dick (et al.) * MacLane, Roland (et al.) (Box 2)
  - Couchville, U.S.A. ( Show #7, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 5/25/59. Writer(s): Brecher, Irving (Box 1)
  - Crazylegs Gillis (Show #14, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 7/7/61. Writer(s): Ryan, Terry (et al.) * Kane, Joel (et al.) (Box 5)
  - Day the Teachers Disappeared, The (Show #11, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/19/60. Writer(s): Reisner, Dean (Box 3)
  - Deck the Halls (Show #16, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 7/28/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 1)
  - Devil and Dobie Gillis, The (Show #36, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 2/5/63. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - Dig, Dig, Dig (Show #7, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/31/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Dobie Gillis - Boy Actor (Show #9, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 6/11/59. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 1)
  - Dobie Gillis, Wanted Dead or Alive (Show #24, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 10/5/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - Dobie Goes Beatnik (Show #4, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 7/1/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Dobie Plays Cupid (Show #31, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/12/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Dobie Spreads a Rumor (Show #26, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 10/23/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (et al.) * Beck, George (et al.) (Box 2)
  - Dobie Spreads a Rumor(add.scene for Show #26:vol.29-32,1959)
    - Draft script dated: 10/23/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Beck, George (Box 2)
  - Dobie vs. the Machine (Show #23, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 10/18/60. Writer(s): Wald, Malvin * Shulman, Max (Box 4)
  - Dobie's Birthday Party (Show #10, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 6/18/59. Writer(s): James, Ed (Box 1)
  - Dobie's Navy Blues (Show #29, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 11/9/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (et al.) * Ryan, Terry (et al.) (Box 2)
  - Dobie, Dobie, Who's Got the Dobie? (Show #4, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/8/61. Writer(s): Amateau, Rod * Pine, Les (Box 5)
  - Dr.Jekyll and Mr.Gillis (Show #13, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 8/16/62. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 7)
  - Drag Strip Dobie (Show #9, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/9/60. Writer(s): Nye, Bud * Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Eat, Drink, and Be Merry - for Tomorrow Ker-Boom (Show #8, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/7/61. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence & Maggie * Kane, Joel (Box 5)
  - Everything But the Truth (Show #34, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/31/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Face that Stopped the Clock, The (Show #12, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/30/60. Writer(s): Fox, Fred S. * Elison, Iz (Box 3)
  - Fast, White Mouse, The (Show #5, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/4/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Fist Fighter, The (Show #19, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 8/11/59. Writer(s): Diamond, Mel * Kohn, John (Box 1)
  - Flow Gently, Sweet Money (Show #9, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 7/6/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - Flying Millicans, The (Show #17, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 8/20/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 1)
  - For Whom the Wedding Bell Tolls (Show #18, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/9/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 5)
  - Frat's in the Fire, The (Show #3, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/4/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 5)
  - French They are a Funny Race, The (Show #37, 1959-60)
    - Draft script dated: 1/29/60. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey (et al.) * Drew, Bernard (et al.) (Box 2)
  - French They are a Funny Race, The (Show #37 w/notes, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/29/60. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey (et al.) * Drew, Bernard (et al.) (Box 4)
  - Funny Thing Happened to Me on the Way to a Funny Thing, A(Show#2)
    - Draft script dated: 5/23/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 7)
  - Gaucho, The (Show #13, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 7/7/59. Writer(s): Elinson, Irving * Fox, Fred S. (Box 1)
  - General Cried At Dawn, The (Show #27, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 11/21/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - Gigolo, The (Show #6, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/1/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 5)
  - Girls Will Be Boys (Show #19(added scenes)v.25-28, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/22/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Girls Will Be Boys (Show #19, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/22/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 5)
  - Goodbye, Mr.Pomfritt - Hello, Mr.Chips (Show #36, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 2/17/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Greater Love Hath No Man (Show #11, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 6/29/59. Writer(s): Kane, Joel * Lloyd, Jack (Box 1)
  - Happiness Can't Buy Money (Show #16, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/3/61. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean * Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Have Reindeer, Will Travel (Show #13, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/29/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 5)
  - Have Reindeer, Will Travel (Show #13(added scenes)v.21-24, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/29/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - Have You Stopped Beating Your Wife (Show #15, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 9/27/60. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Amateau, Rod (Box 3)
  - Have You Stopped Beating.. (add.scn.for Show#15:vol.17-20, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 9/27/60. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Amateau, Rod (Box 3)
  - He Who Gets Slapped (Show #32, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 12/14/59. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 2)
  - Here Comes the Groom (Show #39 w/ notes, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 2/15/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel * Shulman, Max (Box 4)
  - Here Comes the Groom (Show #39, 1959-60)
    - Draft script dated: 2/15/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel * Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - How to Cheat an Honest Man (Show #25, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 10/9/61. Writer(s): Pine, Les (et al.) * Kane, Joel (et al.) (Box 6)
  - Hunger Strike, The (Show #23, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 9/25/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Starr, Ben (Box 2)
  - I Didn't Raise My Boy to be a Soldier, Sailor or Marine (Show#24)
    - Draft script dated: 11/22/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - I Do Not Choose to Run (Show #17, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/15/61. Writer(s): Pine, Les (et al.) * Kane, Joel (et al.) (Box 5)
  - I Remember Muu-Muu (Show #32(added scenes)v.33-36, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 12/21/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - I Remember Muu-Muu (Show #32, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 12/21/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - I was a Boy Sorority Girl (Show #27(added scenes)v.33-36, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 10/30/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - I was a Boy Sorority Girl (Show #27, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 10/30/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - I Was a High School Scrooge (Show #20, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 10/26/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 3)
  - I Was a Spy for the F.O.B. (Show #32, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 1/2/63. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - Iceman Goeth, The (Show #11, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 8/1/62. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 7)
  - It Takes a Heap O' Livin' to Make a Cave a Home (Show #34, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 1/10/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - It Takes Two (Show #2, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 4/15/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 1)
  - Jangle Bells (Show #13, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 9/2/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence & Maggie * Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Lassie, Get Lost (Show #29, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 12/3/62. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 8)
  - Like Father, Like Son, Like Trouble (Show #32, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/12/61. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 4)
  - Like Hi, Explosives (Show #8, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 7/19/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud * Kane, Joel (Box 7)
  - Like Low Noon (Show #20, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 8/25/61. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 5)
  - Like Mother, Like Daughter, Like Wow (Show #30, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/5/61. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 4)
  - Like Oh, Brother (Show #22(added scenes)v.25-28, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 9/19/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - Like Oh, Brother (Show #22, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 9/19/61. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 6)
  - Little Chimp that Counldn't (Show #25, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 11/5/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Live Alone and Like It (Show #31, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 11/19/59. Writer(s): Long, Sumner * Kane, Joel (Box 2)
  - Long Arm of the Law, The (Show #38, 1959-60)
    - Draft script dated: 2/8/60. Writer(s): Karson, Lee * Kane, Joel (Box 2)
  - Long Arm of the Law, The (Show #38 w/ notes, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 2/8/60. Writer(s): Karson, Lee * Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Love is a Fallacy (Show #25, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 10/9/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - Love is a Science (Show #6, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 5/4/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 1)
  - Magnificent Failure, The (Show #15(added scenes)v.21-24, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 7/20/61. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 6)
  - Magnificent Failure, The (Show #15, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 7/20/61. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 5)
  - Marriage Counselor, The (Show #21, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 9/7/61. Writer(s): Pine, Les (et al.) * Kane, Joel (et al.) (Box 6)
  - Maynard G. Krebs -- Boy Millionaire (Show #8, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/2/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 3)
  - Maynard's Farewell to the Troops (Show #5, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 5/18/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max * Amateau, Rod (Box 1)
  - Moon and No Pence, The (Show #23, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 10/10/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - Move Over, Perry Mason (Show #2, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/4/61. Writer(s): Amateau, Rod * Riesner, Dean (Box 5)
  - Mystic Powers of Maynard G. Krebs, The (Show #6, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 7/8/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 3)
  - Names My Mother Called Me (Show #23, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 9/25/61. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence & Maggie * Shulman, Max (Box 6)
  - Northern Comfort (Show #3, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 6/13/62. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 7)
  - Now I Lay Me Down to Steal (Show #28, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 11/28/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Old Goat, The (Show #14, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 7/10/59. Writer(s): Fox, Fred * Elinson, Irving (Box 1)
  - Parlez-Vous English (Show #14, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/18/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 3)
  - Power of Positive Thinking, The (Show #21, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 8/17/59. Writer(s): MacFarlane, Louella (Box 2)
  - Put Your Feet in Our Hands (That's Shoe Biz) (Show #35,1959)
    - Draft script dated: 1/7/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 2)
  - Put Your Feet in Our Hands(Show #35,1959,add.scn.) v.37-39, 1960
    - Draft script dated: 1/7/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Requiem for an Underweight Heavyweight (Show #31, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 12/13/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Rice-and-Old Shoes Caper, The (Show #30, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 12/10/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Richest Squirrel in Town, The (Show #9, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 5/12/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max * Riesner, Dean (Box 5)
  - Right Triangle, The (Show #15, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 7/22/59. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 1)
  - Room at the Bottom (Show #22, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 9/14/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - Ruptured Duck, The (Show #1, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 4/21/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Second Childhood of Herbert T. Gillis, The (Show #21, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 11/2/60. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 4)
  - Second Most Beautiful Girl in the World, The (Show #10, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 6/2/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Smoke-Filled Room, The (Show #20, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 9/12/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Shulman, Max (Box 1)
  - Solid Gold Dog Tag, The (Show #27, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 12/7/60. Writer(s): Reisner, Dean (Box 4)
  - Soup and Fish (Show #33, 1959) (2 drafts, diff.dates)
    - Draft script dated: 12/28/59. Writer(s): Davis, Phil * Kane, Joel (Box 2)
  - Spaceville (Show #28, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 12/12/60. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 4)
  - Splinter Off the Old Block, A (Show #7, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 6/24/62. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 7)
  - Strictly for the Birds (Show #12, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 8/13/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - Sweet Singer of Central High, The (Show #8, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 6/9/59. Writer(s): Marion, Charles R. * Allen, Ray (Box 1)
  - Sweet Success of Smell, The (Show #29, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 11/10/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Sweet Success of Smell, The (Show #29(added scenes)v.33-36, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 11/10/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Take Me to Your Leader (Show #3(2nd copy),in vol. 33-36, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 6/23/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence * Williams, Maggie (Box 4)
  - Take Me To Your Leader (Show #3, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 6/23/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence * Williams, Maggie (Box 3)
  - Taken to the Cleaners (Show #24, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 10/1/59. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - Taste for Lobster, A (Show #18, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 8/19/59. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold B. (Box 1)
  - Thanks for the Memory (Show #21, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 10/5/62. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 8)
  - That's Show Biz (Show #30, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 11/10/59. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 2)
  - There's a Broken Light for Every Heart on Broadway (Show#33,1962)
    - Draft script dated: 1/21/63. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 8)
  - There's Always Room For One Less (Show #26, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 11/14/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 8)
  - This Ain't the Way We Used to Do It (Show #26, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 12/7/60. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 4)
  - This Town Ain't Big Enough for Me and Robert Browning (Show #11)
    - Draft script dated: 6/28/61. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 5)
  - Three Million Coins in the Fountain (Show #19, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 9/28/62. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 7)
  - Too Many Kooks Spoil the Broth, The (Show #15, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 9/17/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 7)
  - Truth Session, The (Show #31, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 12/14/61. Writer(s): Sharpe, Henry (et al.) * Shulman, Max (et al.) (Box 6)
  - Two for the Whipsaw (Show #20, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 9/27/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 7)
  - Ugliest American, The (Show #4, 1962)